Tufts University Prison Initiative of the Tisch College of Civic Life (TUPIT) ReSentencing Journal Submissions UA256
Tufts Archival Research Center
- 2022 accessions, circa 2020 -- 2021; UA256.000001; 679 Digital Object(s)
  - Meas, Charles, circa 2021; UA256.000565
    - Maze visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000566
      Florida; Prisoners as artists -- United States; digital art (visual works)
    - A Letter About Unity in Prison, circa 2021; UA256.000567
  - Meikle, Clyde, 2021 May 28; UA256.000568; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - No Point, 2021 May 28; UA256.000569
    - Antagonism(s), 2021 May 28; UA256.000570
    - Interlude (toward an ending), 2021 May 28; UA256.000571
    - An Instrument of Measure, 2021 May 28; UA256.000572
  - Metcalf, Jerry, circa 2021; UA256.000573
    - Why So Many Men and Women Leave Prison Angry and Bitter, circa 2021; UA256.000574
    - The Universe Ripples, circa 2021; UA256.000575
    - Suicide Watch, circa 2021; UA256.000576
    - Here in the Darkness I Wilt, circa 2021; UA256.000577
    - Harsh Mistress, circa 2021; UA256.000578
    - Take a Peek, circa 2021; UA256.000579
    - Peach Fuzz, circa 2021; UA256.000580; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.43 Megabytes
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; acrylic paintings (visual works)
    - Route 66 Dreaming, circa 2021; UA256.000581; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.94 Megabytes
    - Winter Abyss, circa 2021; UA256.000582; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.75 Megabytes
  - Miel, Tshitungi, circa 2021; UA256.000583
    - Bob Marley War, circa 2021; UA256.000584; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.2 Megabytes
  - Meore, Kenneth, 2021 June 18 -- 2021 June 21; UA256.000585; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Preservation Camp, 2021 June 18; UA256.000586
    - Freedom of its own kind, 2021 June 21; UA256.000587
  - Miksch, Nathaniel, 2021 June 26; UA256.000588; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Smorgasbord, 2021 June 26; UA256.000589
  - Moffat, Shane, 2021 May 9 -- 2021 September 4; UA256.000590; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Holding Onto Childhood, 2021 May 9; UA256.000591
    - The Leviathan Within Our Blood, 2021 May 9; UA256.000592
    - One drop of my Ink, 2021 May 9; UA256.000593
    - See Me Where I Stand, 2021 May 9; UA256.000594
    - Trading Yesterday's Today For Tomorrows, 2021 May 9; UA256.000595
  - Mofield, Jerry L., 2021 June 12; UA256.000596; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Phoenix, 2021 June 12; UA256.000597
  - Molnar, Richard, 2021 June 5; UA256.000598; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - 4.24 @ 4:28: On the toilet, 2021 June 5; UA256.000599
    - Untitled poem, 2021 June 5; UA256.000600
    - Untitled poem, 2021 June 5; UA256.000601
  - Liv Mora, 2021 June 16; UA256.000602; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Autumn's Fall, 2021 June 16; UA256.000603
    - Clouds, 2021 June 16; UA256.000604
    - Coffee Filters, 2021 June 16; UA256.000605
    - Would You Wear My Eyes?, 2021 June 16; UA256.000606
    - Collection of 17 Haikus, 2021 June 16; UA256.000607
    - In the Dark, 2021 June 16; UA256.000608
    - State, 2021 June 16; UA256.000609
  - Azadi, 2021 June 4 -- 2021 August 15; UA256.000610; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Forgive Them, Beloved Soul, 2021 June 4; UA256.000611; 1 Digital Object(s); 34.6 Megabytes
      Colorado; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
    - Teach Me Grace, 2021 June 4; UA256.000612
      Colorado; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Live and Learn: Ballad of a refugee and citizen of Earth, 2021 June 4; UA256.000613; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.42 Megabytes
    - Shakedown, 2021 June 4; UA256.000614
  - Morton, Jammy Lee, 2021 June 3; UA256.000615; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Re-sentence, 2021 June 3; UA256.000616; 1 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
    - Lego law says one thing, judges do the opposite, 2021 June 3; UA256.000617; 2 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
    - Untitled thumbnail sketch, 2021 June 3; UA256.000618; 3 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
    - Untitled thumbnail sketch, 2021 June 3; UA256.000619; 4 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
    - Untitled thumbnail sketch, 2021 June 3; UA256.000620; 5 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
    - Untitled thumbnail sketch, 2021 June 3; UA256.000621; 6 Digital Object(s); 91.6 Megabytes
  - Moser, Ryan M., 2021 May 30 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000622; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - The Betrayal of Time, 2021 May 30; UA256.000623; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.12 Megabytes
  - Moye, John "Komrad", circa 2021; UA256.000624
    - Back to Life, circa 2021; UA256.000625
    - Dear Momma, circa 2021; UA256.000626
    - Fatherless Son, circa 2021; UA256.000627
    - Love Lost, circa 2021; UA256.000628
    - The Struggle Continues, circa 2021; UA256.000629
  - Mullin, Crystal, circa 2021; UA256.000630; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - I'm From, circa 2021; UA256.000631
      Missouri; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Street lights fade, circa 2021; UA256.000632
    - Who will watch, circa 2021; UA256.000633
    - In Hall, circa 2021; UA256.000634
  - Munir, Hasim, 2021 June 29; UA256.000635; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Forced to Defend Myself, 2021 June 29; UA256.000636; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.65 Megabytes
    - Just Us, 2021 June 29; UA256.000637
    - Governors A Racist, 2021 June 29; UA256.000638
  - Murray, Jeffrey S., 2021 June 23; UA256.000639; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - A Doleful Lacuna, 2021 June 23; UA256.000640
    - It, 2021 June 23; UA256.000641
    - Lobstah Dreams, 2021 June 23; UA256.000642
    - For Another Day, 2021 June 23; UA256.000643
    - 3:52 A.M., 2021 June 23; UA256.000644
  - Myers, Ivan, 2021 June 12; UA256.000645; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Death Throes, 2021 June 12; UA256.000646; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.04 Megabytes
    - Human Zoo, 2021 June 12; UA256.000647
    - Cemented, 2021 June 12; UA256.000648
    - Fences, 2021 June 12; UA256.000649
    - Ivy, 2021 June 12; UA256.000650
  - Needles, Quinn, 2021 May 24; UA256.000651; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - The Unexected, 2021 May 24; UA256.000652
      Oregon; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Neff, John, circa 2021; UA256.000653
    - An Unexpected Freedom, circa 2021; UA256.000654
  - Nickell, Josh, 2021 June 7 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000655; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Life, 2021 June 7; UA256.000656; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.02 Megabytes
  - Njoroge, John, circa 2021; UA256.000657
    - Stagnation in California, circa 2021; UA256.000658
  - Orozco, Brandon, circa 2021; UA256.000659
    - Hand turkey visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000660; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.9 Megabytes
  - Ospina, Misty, 2021 June 20; UA256.000661; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Dark nights and endless days, 2021 June 20; UA256.000662; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.00 Megabytes
    - Rise Up, 2021 June 20; UA256.000663
  - Ostio, Salvador, circa 2021; UA256.000664
    - Skull viusal art, circa 2021; UA256.000665; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
    - Time, circa 2021; UA256.000666; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.40 Megabytes
  - Page, Frederick, 2021 June 29 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000667; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Resentencing: An Equal Justice Initiative, 2021 June 29; UA256.000668
  - Paul, Ricky, circa 2021; UA256.000669
    - Unsilenced: The Death of Innocence, circa 2021; UA256.000670
  - Pelland, Bradley, 2021 May 3; UA256.000671; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Life Within, 2021 May 3; UA256.000672
    - Imprisonment, 2021 May 3; UA256.000673
  - Pence, Russell, circa 2021; UA256.000674
    - Dark Reflections Cartoon, circa 2021; UA256.000675; 1 Digital Object(s); 26.2 Megabytes
    - Surrealist Dream Project, circa 2021; UA256.000676; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.60 Megabytes
  - Perry, Paul J., 2021 June 24; UA256.000677; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Freedom Requited, 2021 June 24; UA256.000678
    - The Appellant, 2021 June 24; UA256.000679
  - Perry, Travis, circa 2021; UA256.000680
    - Am I Really 'The Man'?, circa 2021; UA256.000681
  - Pierce, Andre "Dre", 2021 May 15 -- 2021 September 20; UA256.000682; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - The Violence of Carceral Logics, 2021 May 15; UA256.000683
  - Plourd, Joshua, circa 2021; UA256.000684
    - Pieces of Time, circa 2021; UA256.000685
    - Warming Winds, circa 2021; UA256.000686
    - The Mural High Above, circa 2021; UA256.000687
    - Coursing The Past, circa 2021; UA256.000688
  - Presley, Christy, 2021 May 24; UA256.000689
    - My Prison Story, 2021 May 24; UA256.000690
  - Price, Chenelle, circa 2021; UA256.000691
    - My Story, circa 2021; UA256.000692
      Scope and Contents
      This document contains descriptions of drug use and child negelect.
    - Untitled short story, circa 2021; UA256.000693
  - Pyles, Christopher, 2021 May 8; UA256.000694; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Another Day in Hell, 2021 May 8; UA256.000695; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.06 Megabytes
      Illinois; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Quezada, Rickey, 2021 May 31; UA256.000696; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Untitled Essay, 2021 May 31; UA256.000697; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.31 Megabytes
  - Radillo, Ruben, circa 2021; UA256.000698
    - Hand holding sun visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000699; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.0 Megabytes
  - Rains, Justin, circa 2021; UA256.000700
    - Why I Can't Stand the Smell of Flowers, circa 2021; UA256.000701
  - Ramirez, Marcos, 2021 June 15; UA256.000702
    - Surviving Covid-19: Day 4 in Isolation, 2021 June 15; UA256.000703
    - Let My People Go!, 2021 June 15; UA256.000704
    - Reach, 2021 June 15; UA256.000705
    - Tender-hearted Travels, 2021 June 15; UA256.000706
    - Resurrection, 2021 June 15; UA256.000707
  - Randall, Gwendolynn, circa 2021; UA256.000708
    - Tiger visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000709; 1 Digital Object(s); 24.4 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; acrylic paintings (visual works)
  - Rashid, Master, 2021 May 9; UA256.000710; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Dear Mother and Father, 2021 May 9; UA256.000711
  - Ray, Erika, 2021 June 28; UA256.000712; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - This Place, 2021 June 28; UA256.000713; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.16 Megabytes
  - Ray, Robert, 2021 March 30 -- 2021 September 9; UA256.000714; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Proper American English, 2021 March 30; UA256.000715; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.83 Megabytes
      Colorado; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
  - Reed, Lisa, 2020 May 24; UA256.000716
    - Untitled Essay, 2020 May 24; UA256.000717
  - Reid, Nathan, 2021 May 20; UA256.000718; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - How is There Still Hope!, 2021 May 20; UA256.000719
  - Rhyley, AJ, circa 2021; UA256.000720; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Lucas, Me, and Harry Potter, circa 2021; UA256.000721
  - Ricardo, Barbarin, circa 2021; UA256.000722
    - Birds visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000723; 1 Digital Object(s); 15.9 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; watercolors (paintings)
  - Richburg, Qwasheam, 2021 May 6; UA256.000724
    - Redemption, 2021 May 6; UA256.000725
  - Ridling, Danny J., 2021 June 9; UA256.000726; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Abstract Paintings, 2021 June 9; UA256.000727
      Arkansas; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
  - Ritmiller, Kimberly, 2021 June 26; UA256.000728; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Remaining Still, 2021 June 26; UA256.000729
    - The Gift of Now, 2021 June 26; UA256.000730
  - Robledo, Joel, circa 2021; UA256.000731
    - Haiku, circa 2021; UA256.000732; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.4 Megabytes
    - Maya A Bird, circa 2021; UA256.000733; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.6 Megabytes
  - Rodriguez, Marvin, circa 2021; UA256.000734
    - Currency 1, circa 2021; UA256.000735; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.8 Megabytes
    - Currency 2, circa 2021; UA256.000736; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.6 Megabytes
    - Linocut Trading Card, circa 2021; UA256.000737; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.19 Megabytes
  - Anonymous 1, 2021 June 15; UA256.000738; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Rising above the ashes, I was born again, 2021 June 15; UA256.000739
    - I am broken, shattered in a million pieces, 2021 June 15; UA256.000740
    - Facing the cold night, surrounded by darkness, 2021 June 15; UA256.000741
  - Rodriguez, Uriel, circa 2021; UA256.000742
    - Untitled collage visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000743; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.89 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Collages (visual works)
  - Rogers, Paul, 2021 May 2; UA256.000744
    - Untitled Essay, 2021 May 2; UA256.000745
  - Roldan, Luis, 2021 June 26; UA256.000746; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Untitled essay, 2021 June 26; UA256.000747
    - you don't know what you got until you lose it, 2021 June 26; UA256.000748
    - One Day we need to stop, 2021 June 26; UA256.000749
    - in Life, 2021 June 26; UA256.000750
  - Romero, Steven, circa 2021; UA256.000751
    - Chanunka Cartoon, circa 2021; UA256.000752; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.2 Megabytes
    - Spirit, circa 2021; UA256.000753; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.3 Megabytes
  - Ross, Alex, 2021 June 23; UA256.000754; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Frozen, 2021 June 23; UA256.000755
    - Fairy Tail?, 2021 June 23; UA256.000756
  - Saleem, Barutay Abdullah, circa 2021; UA256.000757
    - Black Like Me, circa 2021; UA256.000758
    - The Awakening, circa 2021; UA256.000759
    - True Colors, circa 2021; UA256.000760
  - Smith, Timona, 2021 July 1; UA256.000761
    New Jersey; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - When You Are a Woman Who Visits a Man Who Lives in a Prison, 2021 July 1; UA256.000762
      New Jersey; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Interrupted Flight, 2021 July 1; UA256.000763
      New Jersey; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Visit Room Talk, 2021 July 1; UA256.000764
  - Sanchez, John, circa 2021; UA256.000765
    - A Constellation of Ethos, 2021 June 4; UA256.000766
    - Snail visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000767
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; pen and ink drawings
  - Sanchez, Juan, circa 2021; UA256.000768
    - Untitled fiction, circa 2021; UA256.000769
    - College, circa 2021; UA256.000770; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.1 Megabytes
    - Myth, circa 2021; UA256.000771; 1 Digital Object(s); 19.7 Megabytes
    - Portrait visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000772; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.7 Megabytes
      California; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Mixed media works
  - Sapp, Travis, 2021 June 5; UA256.000773; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Defiant, 2021 June 5; UA256.000774
    - Poisonous Soil, 2021 June 5; UA256.000775
    - Reflection, 2021 June 5; UA256.000776
    - Serrano, Joel, 2021 May 24 -- 2021 September 9; UA256.000777; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - ¡Adicción!, 2021 May 24; UA256.000778
    - ¡Violencia domestica!, 2021 May 24; UA256.000779
    - ¡22 & 2 !, 2021 May 24; UA256.000780
    - ¡Paciencia!, 2021 May 24; UA256.000781
    - ¡Come Romeo y Julieta!, 2021 May 24; UA256.000782
  - Shelton, Ronnie, 2021 June 16; UA256.000783; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Coronavirus Calamity, 2021 June 16; UA256.000784
    - Final Breath, 2021 June 16; UA256.000785
    - Covid 19 Pandemic, 2021 June 16; UA256.000786
  - Sherrill, Lisa, 2021 May 21; UA256.000787
    - My Everything, 2021 May 21; UA256.000788
  - Simpson, Angie, circa 2021; UA256.000789
    - Clout, circa 2021; UA256.000790
    - Recovery, circa 2021; UA256.000791
    - To Me?, circa 2021; UA256.000792
  - Sitsler, Cory, 2021 May 17; UA256.000793; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - My Story, 2021 May 17; UA256.000794; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.06 Megabytes
    - Criminal Justice Reform, 2021 May 17; UA256.000795
    - Alone, 2021 May 17; UA256.000796
      Oklahoma; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Fate, 2021 May 17; UA256.000797
    - Lover Lost, 2021 May 17; UA256.000798
  - Slavinski, Justin, 2021 June 7 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000799; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Common Grounds, 2021 June 7; UA256.000800
  - Smith, Kevin, circa 2021; UA256.000801
    - River visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000802; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.1 Megabytes
  - Snyder, David M., 2021 June 10; UA256.000803; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Parenthetically, 2021 June 10; UA256.000804; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.20 Megabytes
    - Ode to Princess Christmas, 2021 June 10; UA256.000805
    - Untitled poem, 2021 June 10; UA256.000806
    - Kindness, 2021 June 10; UA256.000807
    - Miraculous, 2021 June 10; UA256.000808
    - Haiku a la Noelle, 2021 June 10; UA256.000809
  - Solis, Adam Richard, 2021 June 3; UA256.000810; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - The Dance, 2021 June 3; UA256.000811
    - To Whom It May Concern, 2021 June 3; UA256.000812
    - Louder Than Words, 2021 June 3; UA256.000813
    - Illusive Illusions, 2021 June 3; UA256.000814
    - Myths & Legends, 2021 June 3; UA256.000815; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
  - Southwell, Nathaniel A., 2021 May 25; UA256.000816; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Dominant Institutions, 2021 May 25; UA256.000817
    - War of Race, 2021 May 25; UA256.000818
    - Commenting the Leaders, 2021 May 25; UA256.000819
    - Truth in Reform: Seventh Generation Solutions, 2021 May 25; UA256.000820
  - Steanhouse, Alex, 2021 May 28; UA256.000821; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Systems & Politics Essay, 2021 May 28; UA256.000822
    - All I Know, 2021 May 28; UA256.000823
    - What's Real, 2021 May 28; UA256.000824
    - My Thoughts Exactly, 2021 May 28; UA256.000825
    - Daddy's Little Princess, 2021 May 28; UA256.000826
    - Constant Thoughts of, 2021 May 28; UA256.000827
    - Window, 2021 May 28; UA256.000828; 1 Digital Object(s); 92.1 Megabytes
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Mixed media works
    - Randomness, 2021 May 28; UA256.000829; 1 Digital Object(s); 81.9 Megabytes
  - Steed, David X., circa 2021; UA256.000830
    - ...Choose One, circa 2021; UA256.000831
    - Pain, circa 2021; UA256.000832
  - Stephen, Reginald, circa 2021; UA256.000833
    - Ghost In The Language, circa 2021; UA256.000834
    - Second Chances, circa 2021; UA256.000835
      New York (State); Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Black and Blue, circa 2021; UA256.000836
  - Stromberg, Larry N., 2021 June 8 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000837; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Prison World, 2021 June 8; UA256.000838
    - Mr. Box, 2021 June 8; UA256.000839
  - Sulick, Joshua, circa 2021; UA256.000840
    - Rearview, circa 2021; UA256.000841
    - Roads, circa 2021; UA256.000842
    - Impulsions, circa 2021; UA256.000843
    - Never Give Up, circa 2021; UA256.000844
    - It Can Be Done, circa 2021; UA256.000845
  - Swift, Keith, 2021 May 25; UA256.000846; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Untitled poem, 2021 May 25; UA256.000847
  - Tavarez, Victor A., 2021 June 22; UA256.000848; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - The Etiquette, 2021 June 22; UA256.000849
  - Terry, Benjamin A., 2021 June 21 -- 2021 September 3; UA256.000850; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Dying in Prison, 2021 June 21; UA256.000851
      Missouri; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Basic Prison Cable Package, 2021 June 21; UA256.000852
    - Nights in Potosi, 2021 June 21; UA256.000853
    - The Part of Me That Has..., 2021 June 21; UA256.000854
  - Icon: The poetic one, 2021 June 15 -- 2021 September 9; UA256.000855; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - No Justice No Peace, 2021 June 15; UA256.000856
    - Black State of Emergency, 2021 June 15; UA256.000857
  - Terry, James, II, 2021 May 3; UA256.000858; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Season are the Reasons, 2021 May 3; UA256.000859; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
      Wisconsin; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Butterfly visual art, 2021 May 3; UA256.000860; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.6 Megabytes
      Wisconsin; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pencil drawings
  - Thomas, Andrew, circa 2021; UA256.000861
    - Haiku, circa 2021; UA256.000862; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.6 Megabytes
    - Lyrics, circa 2021; UA256.000863; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.0 Megabytes
  - Thomas, Michael L., 2021 June 15; UA256.000864; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 139)
    - Vision, 2021 June 15; UA256.000865
  - Thompson, Deangelo, circa 2021; UA256.000866
    - Choose your path, circa 2021; UA256.000867; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.5 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Mixed media works
  - Tolbert, Sirita, 2021 May 15; UA256.000868; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 140)
    - Life, 2021 May 15; UA256.000869
    - Turn Back, 2021 May 15; UA256.000870
    - Fake Ones, 2021 May 15; UA256.000871
  - Trigg, Chris, 2021 June 1; UA256.000872; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - My America, 2021 June 1; UA256.000873; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.01 Megabytes
  - Tully, Michael, 2021 June 27 -- 2021 September 1; UA256.000874; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 142)
    - Hot Ice, 2021 June 27; UA256.000875
      Rhode Island; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Short stories
  - Tyler, Danny, 2021 June 2; UA256.000876; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 143)
    - Welcome Home, 2021 June 2; UA256.000877
    - The Mirror, 2021 June 2; UA256.000878
  - Valencia, Ciriaco, circa 2021; UA256.000879
    - Surfing visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000880; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.44 Megabytes
      Prisoners as artists -- United States; Pastels (visual works)
    - Window visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000881; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.91 Megabytes
    - Violin visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000882; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.22 Megabytes
  - Valore Del Cielo, circa 2021; UA256.000965
    - Through the Valley of Shadows, In The Shadows of His Wings, circa 2021; UA256.000966
  - Vanderford, Zhi Kai, 2021 May 10 -- 2021 May 17; UA256.000883; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 144)
    Minnesota; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - My 34 Cents, 2021 May 17; UA256.000884
      Minnesota; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays
    - Still Beautiful, 2021 May 17; UA256.000885
      Minnesota; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Poetry
    - Designated white driver, 2021 May 17; UA256.000886
  - Vargas, Martin, circa 2021; UA256.000887
    - Staircases visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000888
      Michigan; Prisoners as artists -- United States; charcoal drawings
    - Bubbles visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000889
    - Painter visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000890
  - Vinton, Christopher, circa 2021; UA256.000891; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 145)
    - This is the View from the Toilet, circa 2021; UA256.000892
  - Anonymous 2, 2021 May 20; UA256.000893; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 146)
    - Poem 1, 2021 May 20; UA256.000894
    - Poem 2, 2021 May 20; UA256.000895
  - Walker, James, 2021 May 20; UA256.000896
    - Prison Life, 2021 May 20; UA256.000897
    - You learn / Over time, 2021 May 20; UA256.000898
  - Walker, Marquis, circa 2021; UA256.000899
    - Face visual art, circa 2021; UA256.000900; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.5 Megabytes
  - Walker, Vaughn, 2021 May 27; UA256.000901; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 147)
    - One Second of a Moment, 2021 May 27; UA256.000902
    - I Fear No Tomorrows!, 2021 May 27; UA256.000903
    - Broken (The hands of healing), 2021 May 27; UA256.000904
    - I am Not Dead!, 2021 May 27; UA256.000905; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.15 Megabytes
    - Elegant Injustice, 2021 May 27; UA256.000906; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.16 Megabytes
  - Walters, James, 2021 June 30; UA256.000907
    Kentucky; Prisoners as artists -- United States
    - Words Like Water, 2021 June 30; UA256.000908
      Kentucky; Prisoners as artists -- United States; Essays